[whooshing]
[narrator] The recently revived King,
now calling himself Meruem,
headed back to the palace
to recover his memories
with Pouf and Youpi in tow.
[whooshing]
[singer singing in English]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[Komugi] I wish someone would tell me
what's happening.
The sight of it annoys me.
It's the enemy's power, sire.
I think the only way
that we can get it to disappear
is to hurt the enemy himself.
Ah. Interesting.
Then let's find out.
[gasps]
[Menthuthuyoupi] Incredible.
Is that really my…
[explosion]
[gasps]
[Meruem] I see.
[Menthuthuyoupi] I was wrong.
My power was never meant
for me to use.
This doesn't make any sense.
-[Menthuthuyoupi] Huh?
-[gasps]
and for you to know that,
you either saw it used,
or it was used on you personally.
So which is it?
[tense music playing]
So why does the enemy still draw breath?
[grunts]
I want you to tell me
how you deactivated the enemy's ability.
Well?
[sighs]
In exchange for releasing me
from his power,
I agreed to spare his comrade.
[Meruem] Then, after he released you,
[gasps]
Now, Pouf.
Sire.
-[Meruem] Youpi.
-Sire!
Our relationships
have become quite complex.
[both gasp]
It seems that our bodies and souls
have become intertwined,
and, as a result of this fact,
there can be no more secrets
between us.
Let's go.
[both] Right.
[Shaiapouf]
Sire, have you somehow realized
what it is I plan to do?
Was that meant as some sort
of final warning?
Do you sense how my guilt
tears away at me?
I do this for the King!
[segments muttering]
-Find her.
-Find her quickly.
-Hurry up. Find her.
-Hurry up, and find her.
[Shaiapouf] For the sake
of our species…
[segment] Find her.
[Shaiapouf] I do this for the King.
-[segment] There? No.
-Is she over there?
[chatter continues]
Where are you going?
I'm talking to you!
You can't remove A.P.R.
till you beat me!
No, that's somebody else.
There's one who can make himself
and everyone around him invisible.
He looks just like a chameleon.
I don't know his name,
but he's a Squadron Leader,
[both gasp]
Youpi, your own emotional instability,
as well as the traitor's betrayal,
Humans are a steppingstone
meant to help us attain
the next level of evolution,
the perfect sacrifice.
The remnants of human ego
within us are variables,
as long as we consider them
following the explosion.
Was this a result of the blast?
that can still see
and then expand the search.
[Knuckle] Bastard.
I'm not his target. That much is obvious.
He turned back just like that.
Who is he after?
but I don't see how we can
without Meleoron's ability.
I've got to protect Meleoron,
no matter the cost.
that they're too small for me to see.
Unlike his main body,
his segments have to be at full size
for me to see them.
[Shaiapouf] The man with the pompadour
was obviously just a decoy.
They must know that we've made
sense of it by now
and we know the chameleon is a traitor.
In other words, they believe
that's why I've returned,
to dispose of the double-crosser.
Assuming that the chameleon
is concealing himself
and the others as they flee
and assuming
that the woman is among them,
They believe the chameleon is my target.
If only they knew how wrong they are.
They'd never imagine
that I would return to kill the woman
Pitou was trying so desperately to heal.
And if I'm lucky, they may even offer
to hand her over to me,
with conditions, of course.
[tense music playing]
[Knuckle] That little monster's
after Meleoron. He must be.
It would make perfect sense,
because, to them, he's nothing
more than a traitor.
Hold on.
We need to be sure about it.
[beeps]
[Shaiapouf] The door leading underground?
So that's it.
They've realized I know
they can become invisible,
or he fled somewhere else entirely.
That's their plan.
They intend to weaken me
by splitting up my segments even further.
-[segments chattering]
-[segment] No. Over there.
-Over there.
-There.
[gasps]
[tense music playing]
[Shaiapouf] What?
So they want to determine
what my target is. Is that it?
What should I do?
Do I split up my segments
to hide my objective,
No. There's no time.
I've made my decision.
I'll go after the girl!
[Killua] So she's his target?
[Shaiapouf] I only have to kill the woman
and hide her body
from the King for a short time.
My segment can manage that.
I only need a minute!
-[electricity crackles]
-[gasps]
Well, I'm up for a game of tag,
and I can play all night long.
[gasps]
[Shaiapouf] Judging by how quickly
he reacted,
it would be nearly impossible
for me to catch him,
even at full strength.
If I don't hurry, the King will arrive.
What do I do?
[narrator] Pressured by the crisis
he faced,
Pouf came up with an evil plan.
[Shaiapouf] That's it.
I know the perfect magic trick.
[Killua gasps]
What's his plan?
Is he gonna attack me first?
That's gonna backfire.
You've reduced your speed and power,
All of your so carefully laid plans
have already been foiled.
[gasps]
you needn't worry.
The King will forgive you.
I don't know why, but for some reason,
this girl is extremely
important to the King,
So for Gon and for the sake
of our mission,
I can't let the enemy have her.
who was talking with dear leader before.
Does that mean the King is dear leader?
Then who is this,
and who are all the people he was with?
Your twisted sense of justice
is pointless.
You know it will never benefit the people.
Just let me go! You feel weird!
What the hell are you doing?
You're all staticky, and I don't like it!
[Killua] Oh, you think so, huh?
You trust that insect
more than you trust me?
[Komugi] "Insect"? What insect?
What are you talking about?
[Killua groans] I forgot.
-She can't see.
-[Komugi] Let go! Please!
[tense music playing]
[Shaiapouf] Damn it. Almost.
[laughs]
It didn't take long
for the poison to kick in.
If the woman you're carrying
chooses to resist,
your speed is bound to suffer.
[tense music playing]
[Killua] What's going on?
He wasn't aiming for me,
which has to mean
he was aiming for the woman.
He wanted to kill her.
allowing me to kill her,
that's all the better.
Oh, Miss Komugi!
Keep fighting back against your captors!
I will save you soon!
[gasps]
[tense music playing]
[Killua] She's knocked out.
All right, I won't pretend
to know what your deal is,
but what I do know
is that you're really starting
to piss me off.
[electricity crackling]
[upbeat music playing]
[Killua] It's true you might be a segment,
but you were still formed
from the original's cells, weren't you?
I only have to burn them, and they'll die.
Electricity.
I shall lend you a hand.
There's no need to concern yourself.
Your priority should be
regaining your memory, Lord Meruem.
I'll take them just as soon
as my body has returned.
Lord Meruem, feast your eyes
on the scene before you.
[tense music playing]
Does this refresh your memory?
They are here for you.
Each one of them belongs to you!
They belong to me?
You will rule
over these ignorant, inferior creatures
and stand proudly atop the food chain!
The entire world will shine
beneath your glorious light.
This is your divine destiny!
[Meruem] Something isn't right.
Huh?
Something…
is missing, something important.
Something that isn't this.
[gasps]
[Shaiapouf] What are you saying, sire?
You must be mistaken.
Nothing could be more important
than ruling over all life forms.
Maybe you're right.
It was destroyed during the battle.
It broke out not very long
after you had left the palace, sire.
This is bad.
That could be it,
the Gungi board and pieces.
[Killua gasps]
[Shaiapouf] If he sees them,
they'll trigger his memory.
[Killua] He just gave up?
[Gon] Over there.
Let's go.
[Gon] Yeah, but still, thanks.
[singer singing in Japanese]